Melville S. Munro Papers MS036
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Loose prints, 1890 -- 1959; MS036.011; 0.75 Linear Feet; 403 Digital Object(s)
  - Pearson Memorial Laboratory, 1926; MS036.011.DO.05123; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 21)
  - Metcalf Hall, 1915; MS036.011.DO.05124; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 21)
    Buildings; Exterior views; Picture postcards; photographic print
  - Barnum Museum, 1915; MS036.011.DO.05125; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 21)
- Photographic History of Dramatics at Tufts College, 1914 -- 1934; MS036.012; 2.0 Linear Feet
  This series contains four dis-bound scrapbooks containing photographs and clippings from dramatic productions on campus from 1914 to 1934.
  - Photographic History of Dramatics at Tufts College, volume 1, 1914 -- 1925; MS036.012.110.00001 (Box 110)
  - Photographic History of Dramatics at Tufts College, volume 2, 1925 -- 1929; MS036.012.111.00001 (Box 111)
  - Photographic History of Dramatics at Tufts College, volume 3, 1929 -- 1932; MS036.012.112.00001 (Box 112)
  - Photographic History of Dramatics at Tufts College, volume 4, 1932 -- 1934; MS036.012.113.00001 (Box 113)
- Lantern Slides, 1900 -- 1950; MS036.013; 0.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains lantern slides of buildings on campus, of professors, and students taken by Melville S. Munro between 1900-1950.
  This series is arranged found.
  - Lantern Slides, 1900 -- 1950; MS036.013.114.00001 (Box 114)
    This box contains 62 lantern slides. See also Russell L. Carpenter Collection (MS041) in series 005 in box 025, some of the lantern slides in the Carpenter Collection are duplicates of Munro photographs, the photographs need to be completely item-catalogued before item cataloging the lantern slides.
    Students; Professors; Buildings; Munro, Melville S.; Tufts University; Tufts College
  - Lantern Slides, 1900 -- 1950; MS036.013.115.00001 (Box 115)
    This box contains 19 Lantern slides. See also Russell L. Carpenter Collection (MS041) in series 005 in box 025, some of the lantern slides in the Carpenter Collection are duplicates of Munro photographs, the photographs need to be completely item-catalogued before item cataloging the lantern slides.
    Students; Professors; Buildings; Tufts University; Tufts College
- Boston Globe Currier and Ives Prints, 1935 -- 1936; MS036.014; 0.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains a book of clippings from the Boston Globe Currier and Ives Prints.
  This series contains one item.
  - Boston Globe Currier and Ives Prints, 1935 -- 1936; MS036.014.117.00001 (Box MS036 Shared 2)
    Arranged by Prof. M.S. Munro, Dept. of Electrical Engineering. Pulled from Tisch Library March 2009, the original library catalog number was NE2451.M9.
- Tufts College history and technology, 1900 -- 1940; MS036.015; 0.5 Linear Feet
  These six scrapbooks contain captioned photographs that primarily document the Engineering Department at Tufts University between the years 1900-1940, including students, faculty, reunions, and projects. There is an emphasis on documenting the technological equipment, laboratory space, and classroom space in Robinson Hall. Also included are photographs of the Tufts campus and Tufts during World War, I.
  - Apparatus photograph album, 1900 -- 1940; MS036.015.118.00001 (Box 118)
    This date range is approximate. This scrapbook contains captioned photographs of equipment relating primarily to electrical engineering. These photographs were probably taken in Robinson Hall, which housed the Departments of Electrical, Civil, and Mechanical Engineering from 1900-1940.
  - Apparatus photograph album, 1900 -- 1940; MS036.015.118.00002 (Box 118)
  - Electrical Laboratories at Tufts photograph album, 1900 -- 1940; MS036.015.118.00003 (Box 118)
    This date range is approximate. This scrapbook contains captioned photographs of laboratories and equipment in Robinson Hall, including the "Dynamo Room". Robinson Hall housed the Departments of Electrical, Civil, and Mechanical Engineering from 1900-1940.
  - Telephone photograph album, 1900 -- 1940; MS036.015.118.00004 (Box 118)
    This date range is approximate. This scrapbook contains captioned photographs of the telephone laboratories and offices in Robinson Hall. Robinson Hall housed the Departments of Electrical, Civil, and Mechanical Engineering from 1900-1940.
  - Tufts College Interiors photograph album, 1900 -- 1940; MS036.015.118.00005 (Box 118)
    This date range is approximate. This scrapbook contains captioned interior photographs, primarily laboratories and offices, of Robinson Hall, Eaton Hall, and the Old Chemical Lab.
  - Tufts photograph album, 1900 -- 1940; MS036.015.118.00006 (Box 118)
    This date range is approximate. This scrapbook contains captioned photographs documenting Tufts' campus, faculty and student life, with an emphasis on the Engineering department. Also documents World War, I.